A Guide to the Virginia Secretary of Commerce and Trade, Records, 1988-2005 (bulk 2000-2005)
Library of Virginia
- Series IV. Company Files,, 1994-2001., Extent: .70 cu. ft. (Box 2)
  - Williamsburg Crossroads,1997-1999. (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Bering Truck Corp., (Prospects),1998. (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Beretta Corp., (Prospects),2000. (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Orange X, (Prospects),2000. (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Project Blue Bell (Lockwood Greene Consulting)(Prospects),2000. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Project K (Kronotex Inc.) (Prospects),2000. (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Project Slate,(Prospects),2000. (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Scalamandre Silks Inc., (Prospects),2000. (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Siemens Automotive Corp.,(Prospects),1999. (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - SPX Corporation, (Prospects),2001. (Box 16, Folder 9)